<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<copyright>Copyright (c) 2020 Verizon Media. All rights reserved.</copyright>
<description>Latest Financial News for aapl</description>
<image>
<height>45</height>
<link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=aapl</link>
<title>Yahoo! Finance: aapl News</title>
<url>https://s.yimg.com/rz/stage/p/yahoo_finance_en-US_h_p_finance_2.png</url>
<width>144</width>
</image>
<item>
<description>The most beaten up stock, such as travel and leisure names, continue to rally even though stock market futures are down Thursday morning.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">04ffa043-a81f-3548-bd53-eac844cecc04</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/04ffa043-a81f-3548-bd53-eac844cecc04/the-dow-is-going-nowhere-%E2%80%94.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>The Dow Is Going Nowhere — but the Market’s Message Is the Same</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. Chief Executive Officer Tim Cook wrote an open letter on racism, highlighting that his company must do more.The full text of the letter was posted to the iPhone maker’s website.“To create change, we have to reexamine our own views and actions in light of a pain that is deeply felt but too often ignored,” Cook said. “Issues of human dignity will not abide standing on the sidelines. To the Black community -- we see you. You matter and your lives matter.”Cook said Apple would “commit to continuing our work to bring critical resources and technology to underserved school systems,” as well as “fight the forces of environmental injustice -- like climate change -- which disproportionately harm Black communities and other communities of color.”Earlier this week, Cook said in an internal memo to employees that protections for people are “still not universally applied” as he discussed discrimination and inequality in the U.S.Cook made the comments after the killing of George Floyd in Minneapolis that sparked protests and riots across the U.S., later extending to the U.K. and other countries.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2020 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e44300ec-4e26-39c4-8b29-5aed8c673650</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-ceo-tim-cook-publishes-112938774.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 11:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook Publishes Open Letter on Racism, Discrimination</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>European countries cautiously emerging from the onslaught of the coronavirus pandemic are looking to a second generation of contact tracing apps to help contain further outbreaks. The latest apps have big advantages over earlier ones as they work on Apple's iPhone, one of the most popular smartphones in Europe, and do not rely on centralized databases that could compromise privacy. Switzerland, Latvia and Italy have opted for Bluetooth short-range radio for their apps, based on technology from Apple and Google that securely logs exchanges on the smartphones of people who have been near each other.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">54b3b6c8-81a2-36b7-8f95-d50b9c066716</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/europe-pins-hopes-smarter-coronavirus-111118443.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 11:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Europe pins hopes on smarter coronavirus contact tracing apps</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>For the past five-plus decades, Berkshire Hathaway (NYSE: BRK.A)(NYSE: BRK.B) CEO Warren Buffett has been in a class of his own on the investing front. According to Berkshire Hathaway's annual letter to shareholders, released in February, the per-share market value of Buffett's company has averaged a 20.3% annual gain since the beginning of 1965, compared to 10% on the nose for the benchmark S&P 500, inclusive of dividends paid. This difference may not sound jaw-dropping, but the aggregate gain over the past 55 years is 19,784% for the S&P 500 and 2,744,062% for Berkshire Hathaway.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3a3ebbab-ea94-394e-b0e1-6e5719ab3d31</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/3a3ebbab-ea94-394e-b0e1-6e5719ab3d31/buffett%27s-portfolio-hasn%27t.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Buffett's Portfolio Hasn't Done This in 4 Years, Until Now</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Taiwan is dangling incentives to attract more than NT$40 billion ($1.3 billion) of annual investments in research and technology, creating a seven-year blueprint to safeguard the island’s lead in semiconductors and other cutting-edge fields.As part of the initiative, the cabinet plans to allocate more than NT$10 billion to entice foreign chipmakers to set up R&D facilities locally, confirming an earlier Bloomberg News report. The government said Thursday it aims to subsidize as much as half of all research and development costs incurred by global chip companies that build centers on the island.The endeavor escalates global competition for much-sought-after semiconductor technology and is intended to build on the island’s technology industry, led by major players such as key Apple Inc. suppliers Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. and Hon Hai Precision Industry Co. Taiwan has been caught in the middle of a clash between the U.S. and China over the development of chip technology that powers everything from smartphones to 5G base stations.Last month, the Trump administration barred any chipmaker using American equipment from supplying China’s Huawei Technologies Co. without approval, dealing a major blow to TSMC -- the world’s largest contract chipmaker -- and its peers.Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen has pledged to transform Taiwan into an R&D hub for emerging technologies. Her government is now pursuing more foreign tech investments from multinationals seeking to shift out of China over concerns about the intensifying U.S.-China trade war and their desire to reduce dependency on the world’s second-largest economy.The incentive program is mainly targeted at makers of memory chips, though part of it will also be used to attract global 5G and artificial intelligence technology companies.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2020 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">a4abd425-d4a8-3491-ba3f-eaa27cbe5263</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/taiwan-draws-plan-woo-1-043814756.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 04:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Taiwan Draws Up Plan to Woo $1.3 Billion of Annual Tech Research</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>From its Silicon Valley-like campus near Mumbai, Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani's Jio telecom carrier is emerging as a winner from changes in the way Indian consumers plug into a digital economy made more urgent by the coronavirus pandemic. For Indian shoppers who prefer to order online, it is launching a grocery ordering service with Facebook Inc's popular WhatsApp messaging. India's 10-week lockdown has also led to a surge in demand for data, boosting Jio's phone and broadband offerings.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">00222e1c-8cfe-3dd5-83c2-0852e3ecc037</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/focus-amid-pandemic-investors-bet-003000363.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>FOCUS-Amid pandemic, investors bet on India's Jio and its giant-killer playbook</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>A chorus of global criticism has been ballooning against the U.S. over the death of a black man at the hands of policeman last week, and President Donald Trump’s response to the millions that have taken to the streets to protest there.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">ec2f9fe6-f840-3d6a-a82d-f3e9f5b01b31</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/ec2f9fe6-f840-3d6a-a82d-f3e9f5b01b31/from-politicians-and.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>From politicians and diplomats to Pope Francis and stars of European soccer, global outcry grows over George Floyd’s death</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>Among the Dow Jones stocks, Apple and Microsoft are among the top stocks to buy and watch in June 2020.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">65b53896-faf4-3a06-9d0d-a63cf3c83192</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/65b53896-faf4-3a06-9d0d-a63cf3c83192/dow-jones-stocks-to-buy-and.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 20:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Dow Jones Stocks To Buy And Watch In June 2020: Apple, Intel, Microsoft, Visa, Walmart</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>‘Local authorities will be alerted,’ warns a message popping up on stolen iPhones, per social media posts</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">13e97008-7689-36a5-9b3f-88c3dd9d261d</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/13e97008-7689-36a5-9b3f-88c3dd9d261d/apple-is-disabling-and.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Apple is disabling and tracking some looted iPhones</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>A possible activist stake in Boeing lit a fire under the stock, and an analyst sees the App Store helping to drive services growth for Apple.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e526ae03-b189-3fda-b319-19088a5f7830</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/e526ae03-b189-3fda-b319-19088a5f7830/dow-jones-up-400-points-as.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Dow Jones Up 400 Points as Boeing Stock Soars, Apple's App Store Sees Sustained Demand</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>For more investors, low cost index funds, especially exchange-traded index funds, are the way to go. How annuities could protect your retirement income Annuities can help plan for retirement during a volatile market. Maybe you saw the study which found that 10% of retail investors beat the market indexes over time.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">f83de77c-045c-3d23-a072-45b2be505960</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/f83de77c-045c-3d23-a072-45b2be505960/watch-out%3A-this-is-the-age.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Watch out: This is the age where you should definitely stop trading stocks</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>New data suggests life is getting back to some form of normal after the worst of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49b3dd0e-b837-3499-af0b-10c005819118</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/demand-for-all-things-stayathome-may-be-over-goldman-sachs-175212025.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Demand for all things stay-at-home may be over: Goldman Sachs</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>(Bloomberg Opinion) -- One of the most feared antagonists in the “Star Trek” universe is the seemingly unstoppable alien species called the Borg. These cybernetic aliens travel the galaxy, conquering and assimilating everything in their path while greeting each new victim with the catch-phrase, “Resistance is futile.”In many ways, the prevailing narrative around Big Tech is similar to this sci-fi series villain story line. Pundits often cite how the technology giants’ vast financial resources and R&D budgets will lead to an inexorable march to control more and more of the economy. And sure, on the surface it makes sense. Apple Inc. and Google-parent Alphabet Inc. sport net cash balances of roughly $100 billion each and dominate their respective markets, generating vast profit streams from smartphones to search engines. Together with Facebook Inc., Netflix Inc. and Microsoft Corp., these behemoths also reign over the stock market with their ballooning valuations. How can any smaller company hope to compete against such power in the current difficult environment?The reality paints a much less daunting picture. It turns out that the Covid-19 era has led to an explosion of innovation and rapid growth for dozens of smaller technology companies. Many of these upstarts — from video-conferencing software maker Zoom Video Communications Inc. to cloud-computing firm Datadog Inc. — are emphatically winning even as the tech giants try to squash them. And they’re doing it in many cases by simply making a better product and having a laser focus on it. There’s a flaw in the concept that Big Tech can easily expand into new markets by leveraging the power of their core businesses. The reason is all companies – big or small – have finite top-tier engineering talent. And of course, companies tend to put their best people on their most important profit-making segments, versus any peripheral new markets, opening the door for the upstart specialists to thrive.Earlier this year, I wrote how  corporations were flocking to software vendors such as Zoom for solutions on how to get the job done at a time when their employees were forced to work from home amid lockdown restrictions. Since then, Big Tech has taken particular aim at the software company as they sought to push their own video-conferencing tools. Last month, Google added a large, blue-colored “Add Google Meet video conferencing” button any time a Google Calendar user tries to add an appointment, while its Gmail accounts with its billion-plus user base also conspicuously have Google Meet in the lower left corner at all times. Microsoft, meantime, has sought to capitalize on early security concerns with Zoom to promote its Teams product. Despite the aggressive moves, you couldn’t see any negative impact in Zoom’s results. Late Tuesday, the upstart posted April-quarter sales results that crushed Wall Street estimates. The company posted first-quarter revenue of $328 million, up 169% from a year earlier, versus the $203 million Bloomberg consensus. It also projected a sales range of $495 million to  $500 million for the current quarter, more than double the $222 million analyst estimate. Zoom shares climbed 5% on Wednesday, adding to year-to-date gains that already topped 200%.That’s just Zoom. There are plethora of cloud software names — including monitoring analytics provider Datadog and user authentication company Okta, Inc. — that are also seeing surging demand for their services and the soaring stock prices to match. These companies are building out comprehensive offerings and stronger leadership positions in their respective categories that will be harder to displace as they grow in stature. And it’s still early innings on the growth curve for many of these firms. The move to cloud-computing is a seminal paradigm shift similar in scope to the transition to mobile smartphones nearly a decade ago. Gartner said the world-wide enterprise technology market was $3.7 trillion last  year. Even if the economy contracts, it will be a large market, with lots of room for fast-growing companies to make meaningful share gains as spending shifts toward new technologies. “The trends of digital transformation and cloud migration remain very much intact over the long term and may even be accelerated or amplified,” Datadog CEO Olivier Pomel said during his May earning call with investors. Another recent example of Big Tech’s failure is Amazon.com Inc.’s foray into gaming. After years of development, the e-commerce giant released its first big-budget video game “Crucible” last month to much fanfare, even advertising the title on the front page of its website. It was meant to be the Amazon’s beachhead into the large attractive gaming market. It didn’t go well. To illustrate,  just a couple weeks after its launch “Crucible” has precipitously fallen in the Twitch charts, a key indicator of gamer engagement, to roughly 100 viewers or barely in the top 500 titles. It turned out to be a complete flop, even as Epic Games Inc.’s Fortnite remains a fan favorite.Despite the worries over Big Tech’s growing dominance, the flip side may actually be the bigger risk. Last month, I wrote how other retailers appear to be taking advantage of Amazon’s service troubles to make incursions, which has allowed them to grow their e-commerce businesses at triple-digit rates. In social media, the short-video platform TikTok has also surged in popularity. Last week, Bloomberg News reported TikTok’s parent ByteDance Ltd.’s revenue for last year more than doubled to more than $17 billion from $7.4 billion in 2018, a level of sales nearly triple that of Twitter Inc. and Snap Inc. combined. Incredibly, if TikTok continues it current growth trajectory, it has the potential to surpass some of Facebook’s key platforms within a few years. And speaking of Facebook, its latest big push into e-commerce space, Facebook Shops, relies in great deal on a partnership with online-store software maker Shopify Inc. and its extensive array of commerce tools for small businesses.History shows the tech industry’s reputation for disruption is unmatched. And if it is any guide, investors  shouldn’t overlook or underestimate the industry’s up-and-comers, even in — or should I say especially in — times like these. This column does not necessarily reflect the opinion of the editorial board or Bloomberg LP and its owners.Tae Kim is a Bloomberg Opinion columnist covering technology. He previously covered technology for Barron's, following an earlier career as an equity analyst.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.com/opinionSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2020 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">457f1609-4910-3281-98ba-f8ba757b09e2</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zooms-boom-pokes-holes-big-164909588.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Zoom's Boom Pokes Holes in the Big-Tech 'Borg' Narrative</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>Global smartphone shipments will fall nearly 12% to 1.2 billion units in 2020, market research firm IDC said on Wednesday, citing lower consumer spending due to the economic impact of the coronavirus crisis. The COVID-19 pandemic has not only disrupted business supply chains, with major smartphone makers such as Apple Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd flagging financial hits, but also squeezed consumer spending worldwide. "Nationwide lockdowns and rising unemployment have reduced consumer confidence and reprioritized spending towards essential goods, directly impacting the uptake of smartphones in the short term", said https://bit.ly/3036tkj Sangeetika Srivastava, senior research analyst with IDC.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">90be865e-b085-3025-b17e-2f639ad41267</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-smartphone-shipments-fall-12-164155177.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Global smartphone shipments to fall 12% this year on virus woes - IDC</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>Walmart Inc said on Wednesday it shifted firearms and ammunition out of sales floors of some U.S. stores amid nationwide protests over the death of an unarmed black man at the hands of police last week. "We have temporarily removed firearms and ammunition from the sales floor in some stores out of an abundance of caution," the nation's largest retailer said in a statement.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">98eed052-876b-38ed-872f-99a8e8707ef0</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/walmart-removes-firearms-ammunition-floor-161646692.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Walmart removes firearms, ammunition from floor display as protests rage in U.S.</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>Jim Cramer shares stock market news including Apple cutting prices in China for shopping festival, social justice and investing advice during the civil unrest.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">c1471f71-18af-3023-a37f-6f1769371e99</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/c1471f71-18af-3023-a37f-6f1769371e99/morning-bell-with-jim-cramer%3A.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Morning Bell With Jim Cramer: Apple Phone Sales in China</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>The company’s App Store traffic is running well ahead of expectations in the June quarter, according to a new report.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0d39a7e9-e846-3ba4-83d0-3f7e7976b3ae</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/0d39a7e9-e846-3ba4-83d0-3f7e7976b3ae/apple-stock-is-nearing-a.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Apple Stock Is Nearing a Record. Its App Store Revenues Are Soaring.</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>AT&T (NYSE: T) launched HBO Max last week with a couple big missing pieces: You can't watch it on Roku (NASDAQ: ROKU) devices or Amazon's (NASDAQ: AMZN) Fire TV products. CEO of AT&T's Otter Media division, Tony Goncalves, explained the dispute between HBO Max and Roku and Amazon in an interview with The Verge.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4c5f2c4a-9bf6-3b37-aff9-a72d143af549</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/4c5f2c4a-9bf6-3b37-aff9-a72d143af549/why-hbo-max-isn%27t-on-roku-or.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Why HBO Max Isn't on Roku or Fire TV Yet</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>The major stock indexes were higher early Wednesday amid continued civil unrest and payroll data. Apple neared an all-time high.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">c6bf1bee-8d06-38ee-a63c-84a4e1843b55</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/m/c6bf1bee-8d06-38ee-a63c-84a4e1843b55/dow-jones-surges-400-points.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Dow Jones Surges 400 Points On Jobs Data, As Civil Unrest Continues; CrowdStrike, Zoom Video Jump On Earnings</title>
</item>
<item>
<description>Data from Sensor Tower points to Apple Inc. (NASDAQ: AAPL) growing its App Store net revenue by 39% year-over-year in May, and this trend bodes well for the stock, according to Morgan Stanley.The Apple Analyst Katy Huberty maintained an Overweight rating on Apple and lifted the price target from $326 to $340.The Apple Thesis Apple's App Store performance in May could prove to be the strongest year-over-year growth seen since April 2017, Huberty said in a Wednesday note. (See her track record here.)Since the start of the second calendar quarter, App Store net revenue is tracking higher by 35% year-over-year, and this is "meaningfully" higher than expectations for 18% growth, the analyst said. Even if the pace of growth slows down in June, total App Store sales growth could come in at 32% for the quarter, which translates to more than $500 million of Services revenue upside versus expectations, she said. Consumers are showing high levels of engagement with apps as part of a "new normal," and this trend will likely remain for the near-to-medium-term, Huberty said. Consumers will likely continue spending more time indoors, she said. Apple's net revenue per download fell year-over-year from February through April as consumers took advantage of free collaboration and communication apps, according to Morgan Stanley.But the trend improved in May when net revenue per download inflected to a 12% year-over-year growth rate, Huberty said, adding that this is an "encouraging sign" and makes the case for a healthy app economy moving forward.AAPL Price Action Shares of Apple were trading 0.19% higher at $323.94 at the time of publication. Related Links:Martin Scorsese's Next Movie Will Be Financed By Apple: ReportApple Cuts iPhone Prices in China To Push Sales As Country Reopens EconomyPhoto courtesy of Apple. Latest Ratings for AAPL DateFirmActionFromTo Jun 2020Morgan StanleyMaintainsOverweight May 2020B of A SecuritiesMaintainsBuy May 2020Deutsche BankMaintainsBuy View More Analyst Ratings for AAPL View the Latest Analyst Ratings See more from Benzinga * Retail Pro Says Giants Like Amazon, Walmart Will Prevail After Coronavirus: 'It's Not Fair' * Coronavirus Sell-Off A Major Opportunity For Activist Investors * Gene Munster Dismisses Goldman's Apple Downgrade, Says Cupertino Has Long-Term Earnings Power(C) 2020 Benzinga.com. Benzinga does not provide investment advice. All rights reserved.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">122ecd45-6f49-3c53-9f46-3fa16da9406a</guid>
<link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/morgan-stanley-bullish-rising-app-150013256.html?.tsrc=rss</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
<title>Morgan Stanley Bullish On Rising App Store Revenue, Raises Apple Price Target</title>
</item>
<language>en-US</language>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 12:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=aapl</link>
<title>Yahoo! Finance: aapl News</title>
</channel>
</rss>
